我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, we'll ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
求救
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
presisco
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
我理解不了这个动画,兄弟
I don't get this cartoon, man.
它们为什么不干脆把地上的冰淇淋吃掉呢?
Why don't they just eat the ice cream off the floor?
他们没必要哭啊
They don't have to cry about it.
嗷,又来了
Aw, not again.
昨天也出现过这种情况
It was doing this yesterday, too.
等一下,我能搞定
Hang on. I got it.
现在呢?
How about now? Aah.
电视之前从没出现过这种情况
It's never done that before.
通过全频段...橄榄石
On all frequencies...Peridot.
我是橄榄石
This is Peridot,
通过全频段
transmitting on all frequencies
从已废弃的水晶体系殖民地地球发送信息
from abandoned crystal system colony planet earth
致黄钻石
to yellow diamond.
我的任务失败了
My mission has been compromised.
我的护送者与线人消失了
My escort and informant are gone,
而且我现在被困在这里
and I am now stranded.
一定要派遣支援啊!
Please send help.
我是橄榄石,通过全频段...
This is Peridot, transmitting on all frequencies...
好的.谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
康妮说她电视上也是这个
Connie says it's on her TV, too.
但橄榄石能从哪
But where could Peridot
传送这么强的信号?
be broadcasting a signal that strong?
只有一个地方
There's only one place.
狮子,你还好吗?
Lion, are you okay?
正如我所担心的
It's as I feared.
看来橄榄石通过某些手段修复了通讯中枢站
It looks like Peridot somehow repaired the communication hub.
或者,至少也是一部分
Well, at least some of it.
所以...我们只需要再一次砸坏它,对吧?
So we just got to wreck it up again, right?
你们得融合成苏纪石
You guys should form Sugilite.
...是吗?
Yeah?
呃,我觉得,这得看石榴
Well, uh, it's up to Garnet, I guess.
你怎么看?我们要不砸个爽?
What do you say? Shall we mash it up?
不
No.
但...难道我们不需要像上次一样巨大吗?
But...Don't we need to be huge like last time?
上次是场灾难
Last time was a disaster.
上次我们融合时,苏纪石暴走了
Last time we fused, Sugilite went berserk.
而且归功于她我们之后都没法传送到这了
And it's because of her that we can't even warp here anymore.
我会变得草率,你则会变得鲁莽
I could be rash, you could be reckless,
最后我们都会忘乎所以
and we could both get carried away.
所以,这次,苏纪石要下场了
So, for the time being, Sugilite is benched.
我们现在需要的是仔细
What we need now is to be careful.
这次该你和我了,珍珠
It's you and me, Pearl.
咱们融合吧
Let's fuse.
不要哭,珍珠
Don't cry, Pearl.
来吧,一起完成任务
Come on. Let's do this.
我跟着你呢
I'm right behind you.
Whoo-hoo!
融合,融合,融合,融合!
Fusion! Fusion! Fusion! Fusion!
准备
Ready.
等等
Hang on.
恍如隔世啊
It's been such a long time.
此处舞蹈参考自韩国歌手sunmi（李宣美），同时与其歌曲Full Moon同步
观众们晚上好!
Good evening, everybody!
我是可爱的红玛瑙,
This is the lovely sardonyx, coming to you live
在即将彻底报废的通讯中枢为你现场直播
from the soon-to-be former communication hub.
你们今晚怎么样?
How are y'all doing tonight?
好极了
Great.
女巨人!
Giant woman!
噢,我的星星啊
Oh, my stars.
这不是史蒂文·宇宙吗
If it isn't Steven Universe.
我们总算见面了
We finally meet.
那么...你认为呢?
So... What do you think?
等待我值吗?
Was I worth the wait?
我在说什么瞎话啊?当然啦
What am I saying? Of course I was.
喔,你真能说会道啊
Wow. You're so articulated.
你不也是最可爱的小帅哥吗?
Well, aren't you the sweetest little charmer?
我现在真想将你在手心挤挤
I could literally squish you right now.
反正又不难
It would not be hard.
对不起,我实在是太高兴我能来这里了
Sorry. I'm just so excited to be here.
你知道,我最近一直不能做自己呢
You see, I haven't exactly been myself lately.
融合段子
Fusion joke.
我有的,不只是段子
And jokes aren't the only thing I've got.
嗯?哦!
Hmm?  Oh!
你要用你的战锤砸些东西吗?
Are you gonna smash stuff with your war hammer?
"砸"是用来形容
"Smash" is the word one would use
另外一个人会做的事的词
to describe what someone else might do.
现在...
Now...
真正用来形容在下的词是...
The proper words used to describe yours truly are...
明确
"Specific"...
聪慧
..."intelligent"...
精准
"Accurate"...
无瑕
"Faultless"...
优雅
..."elegant"...
得体
"Controlled"...
精妙,风度
"Surgical," "graceful"...
当然还有...
And...
强力!
"Powerful"!
但,是的,有时,我也会,砸东西
But, yes, occasionally, I am known to smash.
现在,大家一定要牢记...
Now, just remember, everybody...
一旦你有求于可爱的红玛瑙,
If you ever have need of the lovely sardonyx,
要告诉珍珠和石榴哦
let Pearl and Garnet know.
我立刻就会出现-真的
I'll be there in a flash -- literally.
你们太棒了!
You guys were amazing!
我们刚才真是这样?哦,那很好啊
We were? Oh. Well, that's good.
我们赞爆了!
We were awesome!
我们为什么不经常这么做?
Why don't we do that more often?
为什么,梨?为什么要对我撒谎?
Why, pear? Why did you lie to me?
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
噢,梨
Aw. Pear.
我会原谅她.你呢?
I'd forgive her. Wouldn't you?
Mm.
喔,嘿,紫晶
Oh, hey, Amethyst.
你要错过"哭泣早餐朋友"了
You're missing "crying breakfast friends."
没什么
That's okay.
我很好
I'm fine.
但这集目前为止非常好看
But it's a really good one so far.
并不
Not really.
别担心,我在录制,可以待会看
Don't worry. I'm recording it for later.
又是这个信号
It's the signal again.
橄榄石!
Peridot.
珍珠,信号又出现了!
Pearl, the signal is back.
又一次?
Again?
我们得回去
We need to get back out there.
好
Right.
史蒂文,狮子呢?
Steven, where's Lion?
紫晶,把头从冰箱里收回来
Amethyst, get your head out of the fridge.
此处“MooMoo Milk”致敬《口袋妖怪》系列中的同名饮料
出发吧,各位
Let's go, guys.
我希望你准备好了
I hope you're ready.
你知道的
You know I am.
这是什么?返场表演吗?
What's this -- an encore performance?
还想见到我,不是吗?
Just couldn't get enough of me, could you?
我们在等什么?
What are we waiting for?
表演开始!
Let the show begin!
也许你更应和她一起
♪ Maybe you're better off with her ♪
我想她更适合你
♪ I think she's better for you ♪
我已忘记我们间的美好
♪ I forgot how great it felt to be us ♪
也许我得意忘形了
♪ guess I got carried away ♪
我只能通过你获得力量
♪ I had to use you to make me feel strong ♪
但现在我不再在乎
♪ but I don't care about that now ♪
我看着我的错误铸成的塔
♪ I see a tower built out of my mistakes ♪
现在已经崩塌
♪ and it all comes crashing down ♪
我还有什么能做?
♪ is there something I can do? ♪
♪ Is there something I can do? ♪
我还有什么能做?
我能否再做补偿?
♪ Can I make it up to you? ♪
橄榄石已经回来过两次了
Peridot's been back here twice,
显然她还会再来第三次,对吧?
so the odds are good she'll come back again, right?
Bam!这样我们就能抓到她了.
Bam! That's when we'll get her.
对啊,Bam!
Yeah. Bam!
石榴肯定会有另眼相看
Garnet will be so impressed.
然后她会觉得我酷回来了!
And then she'll think I'm cool again!
Mm-hmm.
没有...
Nothing...
还是没有...
More nothing...
啊!她在那!
There she is!
不,等等,那只是个奇怪的仙人掌
No, wait. That's just a weird cactus.
我觉得她不会来了
I don't think she's coming.
呃...你在干嘛?
Uh, what are you doing?
如果你让你的眼睛失焦,看起来
If you make your eyes blurry, it looks like
两根手指尖出现了一根魔法香肠
there's a little magic sausage between your fingers.
真是蠢爆了
This is stupid.
这根本没用
It doesn't even work
这样
Try this.
嘿,别乱搞我的...哦～
Hey, don't mess with my -- oh!
当然,即使我们没抓到橄榄石
Well, even if we didn't catch Peridot,
至少我教你了一种挥霍时间的好方法
at least I taught you a great way to pass the time.
蛤?
What?
我感觉看到了什么
I think I saw something.
是橄榄石的逃生舱
It's Peridot's escape pod.
她修好了?
She fixed it somehow?
但我还以为在我们手里
But I thought we had it.
她从神庙里偷出来的?
Did she steal it from the temple?
喔,她在用逃生舱搬运柱子
Whoa. She's lifting the pillar guys.
然后...她在修复通讯中枢
And she's fixing the hub.
她在上面做什么?
What's she doing up there?
放大
Enhance.
嘿,不知为什么,橄榄石看起来有点像...
Hey, for some reason, Peridot kind of looks like...
珍珠?
Pearl?
蛤?让我看看
What?! Let me see.
哦,天哪
Oh, no.
为什么珍珠要重建通讯中枢?
Why would Pearl rebuild the hub?
也许她在试着了解它是如何工作的?
Maybe she's trying to study how it works?
不是
No.
我不觉得是这样
I don't think that's it.
也许她是在试着添加更多的频道?
Maybe she's trying to get us more channels?
哦!
Oh!
这可不好
This is no good.
有什么不对吗?
W-what's wrong?
是橄榄石
It's Peridot.
她肯定又修复了通讯中枢
She must have fixed the communication hub again.
石榴...
Garnet...
通讯中枢又出事了
It's the hub again.
她躲过了我的预知能力
She's evading my future vision.
不管试多少次,我都没法看见我们抓到橄榄石
No matter how many times I try, I can't see us finding Peridot.
快点,各位
Come on, team.
我不敢相信橄榄石带给我们这么多麻烦
I can't believe Peridot is giving us so much trouble.
但这不算什么,对吗,石榴?
But it hardly matters, right, Garnet?
我们能破坏这座塔
We can disable this tower
不管要多少次,只要我们一起,对吧?
as many times as we need to together, okay?
好吧.我准备好了
Okay. I'm ready.
你准备好了吗,石榴?
Are you ready, Garnet?
我知道她在做什么
I know what she's doing. You do?
真的?
You do?
停下!
Stop!
有什么不对劲吗,紫晶?
Is something the matter, Amethyst?
你-你不该这样
You -- you shouldn't.
珍珠,我们看到你了
Pearl, we saw you.
啊?
What?
你得告诉石榴是你
You need to tell Garnet it was you.
一脸蒙b
I don't understand.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这...只是...跟你一起成为红玛瑙真的很有趣
It's just so much fun being sardonyx with you.
怪不得我看不到我们找到橄榄石
That's why I couldn't see us finding Peridot.
等等,听我解释
Wait. Let me explain.
是你一直在修复通讯中枢!
You've been fixing the hub!
真的是橄榄石...
It really was Peridot...
第一次时
The first time.
你骗了我
You tricked me.
不,不不不不,
No. No, no, no, no.
不,我们只是需要个融合的理由
No, we just needed a reason to fuse.
我只想和你多分享几次胜利而已
I just wanted to share a few more victories with you.
那些不是胜利
Those weren't victories.
等等,石榴
Wait, Garnet.
你看,我们相比你要弱小太多
You know, we're so much weaker than you.
和你融合是我们感觉变强的一个
Fusing with you is like our one chance to feel...
机会
Stronger.
不要庇护她
Garnet: Don't defend her.
橄榄石就在地球上某处,
Peridot is out there somewhere,
而珍珠一直在分散我们的注意力...就因为些破事!
and Pearl's been distracting us with nothing.
石榴...够了
Garnet... That's enough.
紫晶,跟我融合
Amethyst, fuse with me.
但...
But...
让我们赶紧结束这一切吧
Let's just get this over with.
此处苏纪石的出拳动作受《大力水手》的Twister-Sock Punch与《任天堂全明星大乱斗》中大金刚的Giant Punch启发
求求你原谅我吧
Please forgive me.
我当然会原谅你啦
Of course I forgive you.
我的天
Man.
该有多好啊,
It sure would be nice
如果这能跟动画一样轻松解决
if things worked out the way they do in cartoons.
是啊
Yeah.
如果的话
It would.
你
♪ You
爱,如你
♪ love like you